<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../../rapidminerreferencemanual/documentation2html.xsl"?>
<p1:documents xmlns:p1="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0"
              xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
              xsi:schemaLocation="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0 ">

    <operator key="operator.ecg_xai:Calculate" locale="en"
              version="6.0.000">
        <title>Calculate</title>
        <synopsis>This is the Calculate Operator, which is to set a compare on the result of a calculation.
        </synopsis>
        <text>
            <paragraph>
                This operator is used to set a compare on the result of a calculation. It has two feature input and calculate a result from them. Then it compares the result with the threshold and add this compare as a Condition Node to the current step model.
            </paragraph>
        </text>
        <inputPorts>
            <port name="In pack" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                The input Pack object, which contains the current step model.
            </port>
            <port name="first operand" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.StringInfo">
                Receives a String object, containing the name of the first operand, which is the first feature of the calculation.
            </port>
            <port name="second operand" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.StringInfo">
                Receives a String object, containing the name of the second operand, which is the second feature of the calculation.
            </port>
        </inputPorts>
        <outputPorts>
            <port name="yes" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new calculated Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to Yes.
            </port>
            <port name="no" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new calculated Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to No.
            </port>
        </outputPorts>

        <!-- description of the parameters and the corresponding values -->
        <parameters>
            <parameter key="Type" type="selection">
                Select the type of the calculation here, ethier + - * /.
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Operator" type="selection">
                Select or input the compare operator for the calculation result here, e.g. > =.
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Right Operand" type="configurable">
                Input or select the right operand here, normally a number, e.g. 5.
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Result Name" type="Optional">
                Input the name of the result here, e.g. "RBBB".
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Focused Lead of First Operand" type="Optional">
                Select the name of the focused lead for First Operand here, e.g. "II". (Doing this will add a lead tag to the first input string of data.)
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Focused Lead of Second Operand" type="Optional">
                Select the name of the focused lead for Second Operand here, e.g. "II". (Doing this will add a lead tag to the second input string of data.)
            </parameter>
        </parameters>



        <relatedDocuments>
            <!-- ... -->
        </relatedDocuments>
    </operator>
</p1:documents>
