<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../../rapidminerreferencemanual/documentation2html.xsl"?>
<p1:documents xmlns:p1="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0"
              xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
              xsi:schemaLocation="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0 ">

    <operator key="operator.ecg_xai:Combine" locale="en"
              version="6.0.000">
        <title>Combine</title>
        <synopsis>This is the Combine Operator, which is used to combine two or more nodes into one node.
        </synopsis>
        <text>
            <paragraph>
                This operator is used to combine two or more nodes into one node. It has a extendable input port, which takes input of different Pack object whose most recent nodes differ, it combines these nodes into one node, and output a Pack object containing the step object with the combined nodes.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>This operator can deal with complex combinations of nodes, such as the AND OR relationships between nodes, it also supports combining several nodes into a group condition where at least N conditions should be met.
            </paragraph>
        </text>
        <inputPorts>
            <port name="In pack" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                An extendable input port, which takes input of different Pack object whose most recent node different from each other.
            </port>
        </inputPorts>
        <outputPorts>
            <port name="yes" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new combined Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to Yes.
            </port>
            <port name="no" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.IOObjects.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new combined Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to No.
            </port>
        </outputPorts>

        <!-- description of the parameters and the corresponding values -->
        <parameters>
            <parameter key="Type" type="selection">
                Select the type of the combination here, ethier "Relation" or "At Least".
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Relation" type="selection">
                Select the relation of the combination here, ethier "AND" or "OR". (Available when "Type" is set to "Relation".)
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="At Least () Satisfied" type="input">
                Input the number of conditions that should be met here. (Available when "Type" is set to "At Least".)
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Result Name" type="Optional">
                Input the name of the result here, e.g. "RBBB".
            </parameter>
        </parameters>



        <relatedDocuments>
            <!-- ... -->
        </relatedDocuments>
    </operator>
</p1:documents>
