<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../../rapidminerreferencemanual/documentation2html.xsl"?>
<p1:documents xmlns:p1="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0"
              xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
              xsi:schemaLocation="http://rapid-i.com/schemas/documentation/reference/1.0 ">

    <operator key="operator.ecg_xai:Condition2" locale="en"
              version="6.0.000">
        <title>Condition</title>
        <synopsis>This is the Condition Operator, which is used to check if a compare condition is true or false.
        </synopsis>
        <text>
            <paragraph>This Condition Operator receive the step object from its parent operator through input Model
                Port, add the compare condition to the step model, and return two new routes which indicates the True or
                False of its compare condition.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>This Operator gets the current step model from the input Pack, create a new Condition Node with
                its data input, connect itself with its parent, and add this new node to the step's nodes list.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>Important: this operator is building the step model, without any calculation or training, no
                results or data will be generated.
            </paragraph>
        </text>
        <inputPorts>
            <port name="In pack" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.Pack">
                The input Pack object, which contains the current step model, the parent where this Pack was generated,
                and the route indicator[Yes, No] from the parent.
            </port>
            <port name="left" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.StringInfo">
                Receives a String object, containing the name of the left operand, which is the first operand of the
                compare condition.
            </port>
        </inputPorts>
        <outputPorts>
            <port name="yes" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to Yes.
            </port>
            <port name="no" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.Pack">
                Outputs a Pack object, which contains the current step model with the new Condition Node added, the
                parent is set to this new node, and the route indicator is set to No.
            </port>
            <port name="result" type="com.rapidminer.extension.ecg_xai.operator.Structures.StringInfo">
                Outputs a String object, containing the name of the result of the compare condition.
            </port>
        </outputPorts>

        <!-- description of the parameters and the corresponding values -->
        <parameters>
            <parameter key="Operator" type="configurable">
                Input or select the compare operator here, e.g. > =.
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Right Operand" type="configurable">
                Input or select the right operand here, normally a number, e.g. 5.
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Result Name" type="Optional">
                Input the name of the result here, e.g. "RBBB".
            </parameter>
            <parameter key="Focused Lead" type="Optional">
                Select the name of the focused lead here, e.g. "II". (Doing this will add a lead tag to the input string of data.)
            </parameter>
        </parameters>



        <relatedDocuments>
            <!-- ... -->
        </relatedDocuments>
    </operator>
</p1:documents>
